{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556679800","data":{"timestamp":" 947556679800"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 6d82d27f-5fbf-4c3b-881b-d4f40e27e1de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-15"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556685871","data":{"timestamp":" 947556685871"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 6d82d27f-5fbf-4c3b-881b-d4f40e27e1de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-15"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556704395","data":{"timestamp":" 947556704395"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 6d82d27f-5fbf-4c3b-881b-d4f40e27e1de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-13"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556715202","data":{"timestamp":" 947556715202"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 6d82d27f-5fbf-4c3b-881b-d4f40e27e1de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-13-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556720901","data":{"timestamp":" 947556720901"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 6d82d27f-5fbf-4c3b-881b-d4f40e27e1de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-13-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556729023","data":{"timestamp":" 947556729023"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 6d82d27f-5fbf-4c3b-881b-d4f40e27e1de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-15-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556735195","data":{"timestamp":" 947556735195"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 6d82d27f-5fbf-4c3b-881b-d4f40e27e1de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_16-10-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 16"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556741235","data":{"timestamp":" 947556741235"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 6d82d27f-5fbf-4c3b-881b-d4f40e27e1de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_16-10-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556746985","data":{"timestamp":" 947556746985"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 6d82d27f-5fbf-4c3b-881b-d4f40e27e1de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_16-10-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556751432","data":{"timestamp":" 947556751432"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 6d82d27f-5fbf-4c3b-881b-d4f40e27e1de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_16-10-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556797823","data":{"timestamp":" 947556797823"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 5f74f64d-ea10-47b7-bbaf-64d5948aed3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556799984","data":{"timestamp":" 947556799984"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 5f74f64d-ea10-47b7-bbaf-64d5948aed3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556834639","data":{"timestamp":" 947556834639"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 5f74f64d-ea10-47b7-bbaf-64d5948aed3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556837089","data":{"timestamp":" 947556837089"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 5f74f64d-ea10-47b7-bbaf-64d5948aed3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556877022","data":{"timestamp":" 947556877022"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 5f74f64d-ea10-47b7-bbaf-64d5948aed3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556879370","data":{"timestamp":" 947556879370"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 5f74f64d-ea10-47b7-bbaf-64d5948aed3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556935240","data":{"timestamp":" 947556935240"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 5f74f64d-ea10-47b7-bbaf-64d5948aed3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556990108","data":{"timestamp":" 947556990108"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 5f74f64d-ea10-47b7-bbaf-64d5948aed3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947556992388","data":{"timestamp":" 947556992388"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 5f74f64d-ea10-47b7-bbaf-64d5948aed3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557024249","data":{"timestamp":" 947557024249"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 5f74f64d-ea10-47b7-bbaf-64d5948aed3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_11"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557042752","data":{"timestamp":" 947557042750"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 5f74f64d-ea10-47b7-bbaf-64d5948aed3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_11"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557042860","data":{"timestamp":" 947557042860"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 5f74f64d-ea10-47b7-bbaf-64d5948aed3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura na Ndovu si marafiki tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557052439","data":{"timestamp":" 947557052439"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 91f696a4-2d11-4931-a638-80b8bffe87d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-y-s"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557056064","data":{"timestamp":" 947557056063"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 91f696a4-2d11-4931-a638-80b8bffe87d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-i-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557059695","data":{"timestamp":" 947557059695"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 91f696a4-2d11-4931-a638-80b8bffe87d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_p-b-a"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557068698","data":{"timestamp":" 947557068697"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 91f696a4-2d11-4931-a638-80b8bffe87d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_p-b-a"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557074200","data":{"timestamp":" 947557074200"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 91f696a4-2d11-4931-a638-80b8bffe87d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_z-b-m"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557079604","data":{"timestamp":" 947557079604"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 91f696a4-2d11-4931-a638-80b8bffe87d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-m-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557092033","data":{"timestamp":" 947557092033"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 91f696a4-2d11-4931-a638-80b8bffe87d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-m-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557096622","data":{"timestamp":" 947557096622"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 91f696a4-2d11-4931-a638-80b8bffe87d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-ch-m"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557100203","data":{"timestamp":" 947557100203"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 91f696a4-2d11-4931-a638-80b8bffe87d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-u-b"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557105250","data":{"timestamp":" 947557105249"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 91f696a4-2d11-4931-a638-80b8bffe87d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-u-b"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557110097","data":{"timestamp":" 947557110097"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 91f696a4-2d11-4931-a638-80b8bffe87d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_i-b-f"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557114886","data":{"timestamp":" 947557114886"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 91f696a4-2d11-4931-a638-80b8bffe87d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-m-g"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557120191","data":{"timestamp":" 947557120191"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 91f696a4-2d11-4931-a638-80b8bffe87d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_y-w-b"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557125957","data":{"timestamp":" 947557125954"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 91f696a4-2d11-4931-a638-80b8bffe87d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_b_y-w-b"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557137325","data":{"timestamp":" 947557137325"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 91f696a4-2d11-4931-a638-80b8bffe87d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_b_y-w-b"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557157417","data":{"timestamp":" 947557157417"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_a_z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557164859","data":{"timestamp":" 947557164859"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_a_z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557171510","data":{"timestamp":" 947557171510"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_b_g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557179128","data":{"timestamp":" 947557179128"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_b_g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557185808","data":{"timestamp":" 947557185808"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_b_j"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557192488","data":{"timestamp":" 947557192488"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_o_b"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557199935","data":{"timestamp":" 947557199935"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_o_b"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557206562","data":{"timestamp":" 947557206561"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_b_i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557214088","data":{"timestamp":" 947557214088"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_b_i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557220740","data":{"timestamp":" 947557220739"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_h_b"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557228178","data":{"timestamp":" 947557228178"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_h_b"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557238505","data":{"timestamp":" 947557238505"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_h_b"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557244725","data":{"timestamp":" 947557244725"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_e_r"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557252180","data":{"timestamp":" 947557252179"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_e_r"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557262507","data":{"timestamp":" 947557262507"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_e_r"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557269141","data":{"timestamp":" 947557269141"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_r_m"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557275815","data":{"timestamp":" 947557275814"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_g_b"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557283298","data":{"timestamp":" 947557283298"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_g_b"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557292283","data":{"timestamp":" 947557292282"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 85f9f240-c52c-4cf4-a21e-81bbd6a9e38b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_ch_g_b"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557334078","data":{"timestamp":" 947557334078"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 4f62aa19-91c6-43f2-a10a-9020bac8c666"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_58"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557337457","data":{"timestamp":" 947557337457"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 4f62aa19-91c6-43f2-a10a-9020bac8c666"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_58"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557385391","data":{"timestamp":" 947557385391"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 4f62aa19-91c6-43f2-a10a-9020bac8c666"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_58"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557387748","data":{"timestamp":" 947557387747"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 4f62aa19-91c6-43f2-a10a-9020bac8c666"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_58"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557440576","data":{"timestamp":" 947557440576"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 4f62aa19-91c6-43f2-a10a-9020bac8c666"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_58"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557473109","data":{"timestamp":" 947557473109"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 4f62aa19-91c6-43f2-a10a-9020bac8c666"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_58"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557475322","data":{"timestamp":" 947557475322"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 4f62aa19-91c6-43f2-a10a-9020bac8c666"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_58"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557539469","data":{"timestamp":" 947557539469"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 4f62aa19-91c6-43f2-a10a-9020bac8c666"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_58"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557616219","data":{"timestamp":" 947557616218"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 4f62aa19-91c6-43f2-a10a-9020bac8c666"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_58"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557616302","data":{"timestamp":" 947557616302"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 4f62aa19-91c6-43f2-a10a-9020bac8c666"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_58"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAADUI"," userResponse":" MAADUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557625599","data":{"timestamp":" 947557625599"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-m-g"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557628959","data":{"timestamp":" 947557628959"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_i-b-f"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557634083","data":{"timestamp":" 947557634083"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_i-b-f"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557638203","data":{"timestamp":" 947557638203"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_z-b-m"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557642384","data":{"timestamp":" 947557642384"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-i-p"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557645400","data":{"timestamp":" 947557645400"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-m-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557653100","data":{"timestamp":" 947557653099"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-m-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557664321","data":{"timestamp":" 947557664321"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-m-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557672243","data":{"timestamp":" 947557672243"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-y-s"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557676474","data":{"timestamp":" 947557676474"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-u-b"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557681464","data":{"timestamp":" 947557681463"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-u-b"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557685636","data":{"timestamp":" 947557685636"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-ch-m"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557689517","data":{"timestamp":" 947557689517"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_y-w-b"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557693553","data":{"timestamp":" 947557693553"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_p-b-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557699315","data":{"timestamp":" 947557699314"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_b_p-b-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557739869","data":{"timestamp":" 947557739869"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_b_p-b-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557745463","data":{"timestamp":" 947557745463"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 916b23d8-b216-4a54-b724-7c32bda54f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_b_p-b-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557796836","data":{"timestamp":" 947557796836"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0737dab5-5ca3-4b5e-8956-c1bfb217dada"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wingi_wingi-fulani-maridadi-kumbe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" wingi"," userResponse":" wingi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557822445","data":{"timestamp":" 947557822445"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0737dab5-5ca3-4b5e-8956-c1bfb217dada"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" miguu_pamoja-lazima-miguu-lazima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" pamoja"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557825381","data":{"timestamp":" 947557825381"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0737dab5-5ca3-4b5e-8956-c1bfb217dada"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" miguu_pamoja-lazima-miguu-lazima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" lazima"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557828488","data":{"timestamp":" 947557828488"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0737dab5-5ca3-4b5e-8956-c1bfb217dada"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" miguu_pamoja-lazima-miguu-lazima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" lazima"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557831155","data":{"timestamp":" 947557831155"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0737dab5-5ca3-4b5e-8956-c1bfb217dada"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" miguu_pamoja-lazima-miguu-lazima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" miguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557857894","data":{"timestamp":" 947557857894"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0737dab5-5ca3-4b5e-8956-c1bfb217dada"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mno_mno-kelele-upepo-njiani"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mno"," userResponse":" njiani"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557861162","data":{"timestamp":" 947557861162"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0737dab5-5ca3-4b5e-8956-c1bfb217dada"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mno_mno-kelele-upepo-njiani"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mno"," userResponse":" upepo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557863979","data":{"timestamp":" 947557863979"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0737dab5-5ca3-4b5e-8956-c1bfb217dada"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mno_mno-kelele-upepo-njiani"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mno"," userResponse":" kelele"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557866654","data":{"timestamp":" 947557866654"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0737dab5-5ca3-4b5e-8956-c1bfb217dada"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mno_mno-kelele-upepo-njiani"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mno"," userResponse":" mno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557909522","data":{"timestamp":" 947557909522"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0737dab5-5ca3-4b5e-8956-c1bfb217dada"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbio_kichwa-nia-mbio-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mbio"," userResponse":" kichwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557912194","data":{"timestamp":" 947557912194"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0737dab5-5ca3-4b5e-8956-c1bfb217dada"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbio_kichwa-nia-mbio-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mbio"," userResponse":" nia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947557914883","data":{"timestamp":" 947557914883"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0737dab5-5ca3-4b5e-8956-c1bfb217dada"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbio_kichwa-nia-mbio-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mbio"," userResponse":" mbio"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558001783","data":{"timestamp":" 947558001783"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0737dab5-5ca3-4b5e-8956-c1bfb217dada"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mbio_kichwa-nia-mbio-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558001869","data":{"timestamp":" 947558001869"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0737dab5-5ca3-4b5e-8956-c1bfb217dada"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558007699","data":{"timestamp":" 947558007699"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0737dab5-5ca3-4b5e-8956-c1bfb217dada"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558014210","data":{"timestamp":" 947558014210"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0737dab5-5ca3-4b5e-8956-c1bfb217dada"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_56"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alimhimiza Ndovu aendelea hivyo hivyo maanake hivyo tu ndivyo miguu yake ingelikuwa myembamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558025307","data":{"timestamp":" 947558025307"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 3ced86c7-072a-43c5-8dac-55ea41a693a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558028080","data":{"timestamp":" 947558028080"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 3ced86c7-072a-43c5-8dac-55ea41a693a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558029631","data":{"timestamp":" 947558029630"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 3ced86c7-072a-43c5-8dac-55ea41a693a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558032583","data":{"timestamp":" 947558032583"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 3ced86c7-072a-43c5-8dac-55ea41a693a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558034142","data":{"timestamp":" 947558034142"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 3ced86c7-072a-43c5-8dac-55ea41a693a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558037006","data":{"timestamp":" 947558037006"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 3ced86c7-072a-43c5-8dac-55ea41a693a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558038568","data":{"timestamp":" 947558038568"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 3ced86c7-072a-43c5-8dac-55ea41a693a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558049973","data":{"timestamp":" 947558049972"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 3ced86c7-072a-43c5-8dac-55ea41a693a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558050093","data":{"timestamp":" 947558050093"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 3ced86c7-072a-43c5-8dac-55ea41a693a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558058127","data":{"timestamp":" 947558058126"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 3ced86c7-072a-43c5-8dac-55ea41a693a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558065531","data":{"timestamp":" 947558065531"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 3ced86c7-072a-43c5-8dac-55ea41a693a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558075827","data":{"timestamp":" 947558075827"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 3ced86c7-072a-43c5-8dac-55ea41a693a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558086375","data":{"timestamp":" 947558086374"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558089977","data":{"timestamp":" 947558089976"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558095220","data":{"timestamp":" 947558095220"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558128457","data":{"timestamp":" 947558128457"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558135190","data":{"timestamp":" 947558135190"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558144720","data":{"timestamp":" 947558144720"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558154482","data":{"timestamp":" 947558154482"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558161736","data":{"timestamp":" 947558161736"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558191726","data":{"timestamp":" 947558191726"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558195472","data":{"timestamp":" 947558195472"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558202256","data":{"timestamp":" 947558202256"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558236499","data":{"timestamp":" 947558236499"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558255487","data":{"timestamp":" 947558255487"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558259660","data":{"timestamp":" 947558259659"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558267049","data":{"timestamp":" 947558267049"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558288799","data":{"timestamp":" 947558288799"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558303897","data":{"timestamp":" 947558303897"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558312736","data":{"timestamp":" 947558312736"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558329421","data":{"timestamp":" 947558329420"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558335828","data":{"timestamp":" 947558335828"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558336331","data":{"timestamp":" 947558336331"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558342017","data":{"timestamp":" 947558342016"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 0cd622a3-10f9-4fb0-a76a-54b84ad2dc5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558353787","data":{"timestamp":" 947558353786"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558355923","data":{"timestamp":" 947558355922"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558358049","data":{"timestamp":" 947558358049"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558361315","data":{"timestamp":" 947558361314"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558363608","data":{"timestamp":" 947558363607"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558365857","data":{"timestamp":" 947558365856"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558368743","data":{"timestamp":" 947558368742"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558370997","data":{"timestamp":" 947558370996"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558373191","data":{"timestamp":" 947558373190"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558376378","data":{"timestamp":" 947558376378"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558378444","data":{"timestamp":" 947558378444"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558380549","data":{"timestamp":" 947558380548"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558383584","data":{"timestamp":" 947558383583"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558385801","data":{"timestamp":" 947558385801"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558388008","data":{"timestamp":" 947558388008"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558391056","data":{"timestamp":" 947558391051"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558393399","data":{"timestamp":" 947558393399"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558395740","data":{"timestamp":" 947558395739"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558398800","data":{"timestamp":" 947558398800"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558400921","data":{"timestamp":" 947558400921"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558403017","data":{"timestamp":" 947558403017"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558406143","data":{"timestamp":" 947558406142"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558408344","data":{"timestamp":" 947558408343"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558410513","data":{"timestamp":" 947558410512"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558413669","data":{"timestamp":" 947558413669"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558416100","data":{"timestamp":" 947558416099"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558418503","data":{"timestamp":" 947558418503"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558421717","data":{"timestamp":" 947558421717"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558423988","data":{"timestamp":" 947558423987"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558426240","data":{"timestamp":" 947558426240"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558429219","data":{"timestamp":" 947558429218"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558431447","data":{"timestamp":" 947558431446"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558433681","data":{"timestamp":" 947558433680"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558436597","data":{"timestamp":" 947558436597"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558438956","data":{"timestamp":" 947558438956"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558441303","data":{"timestamp":" 947558441302"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558444441","data":{"timestamp":" 947558444441"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558446840","data":{"timestamp":" 947558446839"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558449242","data":{"timestamp":" 947558449242"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558452253","data":{"timestamp":" 947558452252"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558454507","data":{"timestamp":" 947558454506"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558456815","data":{"timestamp":" 947558456813"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558460079","data":{"timestamp":" 947558460079"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558462307","data":{"timestamp":" 947558462307"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558464528","data":{"timestamp":" 947558464527"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558467878","data":{"timestamp":" 947558467878"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558470358","data":{"timestamp":" 947558470358"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558472825","data":{"timestamp":" 947558472824"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558475606","data":{"timestamp":" 947558475606"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558477790","data":{"timestamp":" 947558477789"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558479987","data":{"timestamp":" 947558479987"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558483392","data":{"timestamp":" 947558483392"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558485749","data":{"timestamp":" 947558485748"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558488107","data":{"timestamp":" 947558488106"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558491250","data":{"timestamp":" 947558491250"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558493507","data":{"timestamp":" 947558493506"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558495829","data":{"timestamp":" 947558495828"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558498927","data":{"timestamp":" 947558498927"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558501065","data":{"timestamp":" 947558501064"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558503200","data":{"timestamp":" 947558503199"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558506333","data":{"timestamp":" 947558506333"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558508603","data":{"timestamp":" 947558508602"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558510893","data":{"timestamp":" 947558510892"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558514091","data":{"timestamp":" 947558514091"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558516360","data":{"timestamp":" 947558516360"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558518587","data":{"timestamp":" 947558518584"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558521839","data":{"timestamp":" 947558521839"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558524184","data":{"timestamp":" 947558524184"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558526548","data":{"timestamp":" 947558526547"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558529716","data":{"timestamp":" 947558529715"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558532102","data":{"timestamp":" 947558532101"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558534468","data":{"timestamp":" 947558534466"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558537872","data":{"timestamp":" 947558537871"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558537966","data":{"timestamp":" 947558537966"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558558084","data":{"timestamp":" 947558558083"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" d086c210-9910-4a96-9151-1f0eba16adc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558569653","data":{"timestamp":" 947558569653"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558576812","data":{"timestamp":" 947558576812"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558578384","data":{"timestamp":" 947558578384"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558582179","data":{"timestamp":" 947558582179"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558583749","data":{"timestamp":" 947558583748"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558588284","data":{"timestamp":" 947558588284"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558589877","data":{"timestamp":" 947558589877"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" choo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOO"," userResponse":" CHOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558592882","data":{"timestamp":" 947558592881"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" choo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558594441","data":{"timestamp":" 947558594440"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558600196","data":{"timestamp":" 947558600196"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558601763","data":{"timestamp":" 947558601763"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558608719","data":{"timestamp":" 947558608718"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558611775","data":{"timestamp":" 947558611775"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chombo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOMBO"," userResponse":" CHOMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558614911","data":{"timestamp":" 947558614911"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chombo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558616472","data":{"timestamp":" 947558616472"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chipsi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIPSI"," userResponse":" CHIPSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558620011","data":{"timestamp":" 947558620011"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chipsi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIPSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558621579","data":{"timestamp":" 947558621579"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558627944","data":{"timestamp":" 947558627944"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558629951","data":{"timestamp":" 947558629951"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558630157","data":{"timestamp":" 947558630157"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 285db3b4-c8a9-43c7-96eb-042d2aa2469a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558643008","data":{"timestamp":" 947558643008"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558643622","data":{"timestamp":" 947558643622"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558643837","data":{"timestamp":" 947558643837"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558644520","data":{"timestamp":" 947558644520"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABASI"," userResponse":" MABASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558645274","data":{"timestamp":" 947558645274"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558645788","data":{"timestamp":" 947558645788"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWETU"," userResponse":" MWETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558646881","data":{"timestamp":" 947558646881"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIJAA"," userResponse":" KILIJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558647808","data":{"timestamp":" 947558647807"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" SHUGHULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558648193","data":{"timestamp":" 947558648193"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558648639","data":{"timestamp":" 947558648639"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558648845","data":{"timestamp":" 947558648844"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558649540","data":{"timestamp":" 947558649540"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABASI"," userResponse":" MABASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558651837","data":{"timestamp":" 947558651837"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558652271","data":{"timestamp":" 947558652271"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558653045","data":{"timestamp":" 947558653045"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558653939","data":{"timestamp":" 947558653939"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIMEJAZA"," userResponse":" ZIMEJAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558654783","data":{"timestamp":" 947558654783"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558657269","data":{"timestamp":" 947558657269"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558658084","data":{"timestamp":" 947558658084"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558658308","data":{"timestamp":" 947558658308"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558658992","data":{"timestamp":" 947558658992"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558659677","data":{"timestamp":" 947558659677"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558659772","data":{"timestamp":" 947558659772"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558660579","data":{"timestamp":" 947558660579"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPAKIA"," userResponse":" KUPAKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558663332","data":{"timestamp":" 947558663332"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" KONDAKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558664246","data":{"timestamp":" 947558664246"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIITA"," userResponse":" WALIITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558664979","data":{"timestamp":" 947558664979"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJINA"," userResponse":" MAJINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558665993","data":{"timestamp":" 947558665993"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558666106","data":{"timestamp":" 947558666106"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558666889","data":{"timestamp":" 947558666889"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558667603","data":{"timestamp":" 947558667603"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558668787","data":{"timestamp":" 947558668787"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIELEKEA"," userResponse":" ZILIELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558672000","data":{"timestamp":" 947558672000"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558674673","data":{"timestamp":" 947558674673"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558676919","data":{"timestamp":" 947558676919"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558677932","data":{"timestamp":" 947558677932"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGHARIBI"," userResponse":" MAGHARIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558680757","data":{"timestamp":" 947558680757"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISIKIA"," userResponse":" NILISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558681540","data":{"timestamp":" 947558681540"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" KONDAKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558682303","data":{"timestamp":" 947558682303"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIITA"," userResponse":" AKIITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558682546","data":{"timestamp":" 947558682546"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558683160","data":{"timestamp":" 947558683160"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558685519","data":{"timestamp":" 947558685519"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558685973","data":{"timestamp":" 947558685973"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558686456","data":{"timestamp":" 947558686456"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558687529","data":{"timestamp":" 947558687529"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIYOHITAJI"," userResponse":" NILIYOHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558688343","data":{"timestamp":" 947558688343"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558688847","data":{"timestamp":" 947558688847"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558689551","data":{"timestamp":" 947558689551"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USAFIRI"," userResponse":" USAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558690005","data":{"timestamp":" 947558690005"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558692789","data":{"timestamp":" 947558692789"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558692944","data":{"timestamp":" 947558692943"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558693427","data":{"timestamp":" 947558693427"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558694092","data":{"timestamp":" 947558694092"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" JIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558694736","data":{"timestamp":" 947558694736"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558695382","data":{"timestamp":" 947558695382"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558695975","data":{"timestamp":" 947558695975"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJAA"," userResponse":" KUJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558696800","data":{"timestamp":" 947558696799"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558697194","data":{"timestamp":" 947558697194"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558697968","data":{"timestamp":" 947558697967"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558699702","data":{"timestamp":" 947558699702"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIJISHUGHULISHA"," userResponse":" WALIJISHUGHULISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558700485","data":{"timestamp":" 947558700485"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAKA"," userResponse":" KUTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558701169","data":{"timestamp":" 947558701169"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558703768","data":{"timestamp":" 947558703768"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558704124","data":{"timestamp":" 947558704123"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558705149","data":{"timestamp":" 947558705149"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPAKIA"," userResponse":" WALIPAKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558706014","data":{"timestamp":" 947558706014"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558706718","data":{"timestamp":" 947558706718"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558706852","data":{"timestamp":" 947558706852"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558707336","data":{"timestamp":" 947558707336"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558709804","data":{"timestamp":" 947558709804"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558710827","data":{"timestamp":" 947558710827"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIWEKA"," userResponse":" WALIIWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558711379","data":{"timestamp":" 947558711379"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558712125","data":{"timestamp":" 947558712125"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558712249","data":{"timestamp":" 947558712249"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558712590","data":{"timestamp":" 947558712589"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558715847","data":{"timestamp":" 947558715846"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558716439","data":{"timestamp":" 947558716438"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPYA"," userResponse":" WAPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558717209","data":{"timestamp":" 947558717209"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISHIKA"," userResponse":" WALISHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558717713","data":{"timestamp":" 947558717713"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKETI"," userResponse":" TIKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558718379","data":{"timestamp":" 947558718378"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558719082","data":{"timestamp":" 947558719082"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558720062","data":{"timestamp":" 947558720060"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" WAKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558720654","data":{"timestamp":" 947558720653"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558720867","data":{"timestamp":" 947558720867"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558721502","data":{"timestamp":" 947558721502"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKAA"," userResponse":" KUKAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558724155","data":{"timestamp":" 947558724155"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558725011","data":{"timestamp":" 947558725010"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558725272","data":{"timestamp":" 947558725271"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558725877","data":{"timestamp":" 947558725876"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558726508","data":{"timestamp":" 947558726508"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558728199","data":{"timestamp":" 947558728199"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWATAYARISHA"," userResponse":" WALIWATAYARISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558728374","data":{"timestamp":" 947558728374"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558728998","data":{"timestamp":" 947558728998"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558729364","data":{"timestamp":" 947558729364"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558729727","data":{"timestamp":" 947558729727"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558733585","data":{"timestamp":" 947558733585"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPENYEZA"," userResponse":" NILIPENYEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558734130","data":{"timestamp":" 947558734130"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558734915","data":{"timestamp":" 947558734914"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKAKAA"," userResponse":" NIKAKAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558735470","data":{"timestamp":" 947558735469"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558735647","data":{"timestamp":" 947558735646"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558736257","data":{"timestamp":" 947558736256"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHA"," userResponse":" DIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558738584","data":{"timestamp":" 947558738584"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558739427","data":{"timestamp":" 947558739427"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKETI"," userResponse":" ALIYEKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558739954","data":{"timestamp":" 947558739953"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558740564","data":{"timestamp":" 947558740564"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558741456","data":{"timestamp":" 947558741455"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHIKA"," userResponse":" ALISHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558741985","data":{"timestamp":" 947558741985"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558742241","data":{"timestamp":" 947558742240"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558743144","data":{"timestamp":" 947558743144"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PLASTIKI"," userResponse":" PLASTIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558743562","data":{"timestamp":" 947558743562"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558744128","data":{"timestamp":" 947558744127"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558744842","data":{"timestamp":" 947558744842"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558747416","data":{"timestamp":" 947558747415"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVAA"," userResponse":" ALIVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558748407","data":{"timestamp":" 947558748407"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558749355","data":{"timestamp":" 947558749354"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOZEEKA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOZEEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558750162","data":{"timestamp":" 947558750160"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOTI"," userResponse":" KOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558750766","data":{"timestamp":" 947558750766"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUKUU"," userResponse":" KUUKUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558751515","data":{"timestamp":" 947558751515"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558752572","data":{"timestamp":" 947558752571"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONEKANA"," userResponse":" ALIONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558752973","data":{"timestamp":" 947558752973"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558753262","data":{"timestamp":" 947558753262"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558754034","data":{"timestamp":" 947558754034"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIWASI"," userResponse":" WASIWASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558757584","data":{"timestamp":" 947558757583"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANGALIA"," userResponse":" NILIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558758239","data":{"timestamp":" 947558758239"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558758703","data":{"timestamp":" 947558758703"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558759508","data":{"timestamp":" 947558759507"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAMBUA"," userResponse":" KUTAMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558760226","data":{"timestamp":" 947558760226"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558761300","data":{"timestamp":" 947558761299"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558762183","data":{"timestamp":" 947558762182"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAONDOKA"," userResponse":" NAONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558763063","data":{"timestamp":" 947558763063"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558763846","data":{"timestamp":" 947558763846"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGU"," userResponse":" MWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558764639","data":{"timestamp":" 947558764639"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558765279","data":{"timestamp":" 947558765278"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAPO"," userResponse":" AMBAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558766368","data":{"timestamp":" 947558766368"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILILELEWA"," userResponse":" NILILELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558768974","data":{"timestamp":" 947558768973"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558769632","data":{"timestamp":" 947558769631"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAENDA"," userResponse":" NAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558770248","data":{"timestamp":" 947558770248"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558770691","data":{"timestamp":" 947558770691"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558771274","data":{"timestamp":" 947558771274"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558774799","data":{"timestamp":" 947558774799"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPAKIAJI"," userResponse":" UPAKIAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558775455","data":{"timestamp":" 947558775454"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558776931","data":{"timestamp":" 947558776931"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAMILIKA"," userResponse":" ULIKAMILIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558777541","data":{"timestamp":" 947558777540"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558778220","data":{"timestamp":" 947558778219"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558778838","data":{"timestamp":" 947558778838"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAWA"," userResponse":" WAKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558779774","data":{"timestamp":" 947558779773"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEKETI"," userResponse":" WAMEKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558782558","data":{"timestamp":" 947558782558"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHUUZI"," userResponse":" WACHUUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558783455","data":{"timestamp":" 947558783454"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIZIDI"," userResponse":" WALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558784714","data":{"timestamp":" 947558784714"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSUKUMANA"," userResponse":" KUSUKUMANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558785754","data":{"timestamp":" 947558785753"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAKA"," userResponse":" KUTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558786541","data":{"timestamp":" 947558786541"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUINGIA"," userResponse":" KUINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558787160","data":{"timestamp":" 947558787159"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558787319","data":{"timestamp":" 947558787318"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558787943","data":{"timestamp":" 947558787943"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558788666","data":{"timestamp":" 947558788666"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558789182","data":{"timestamp":" 947558789181"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAUZE"," userResponse":" WAUZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558789823","data":{"timestamp":" 947558789823"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDHAA"," userResponse":" BIDHAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558790342","data":{"timestamp":" 947558790341"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558792502","data":{"timestamp":" 947558792501"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558793288","data":{"timestamp":" 947558793288"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558794411","data":{"timestamp":" 947558794411"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAJA"," userResponse":" ALITAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558794619","data":{"timestamp":" 947558794619"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558795389","data":{"timestamp":" 947558795389"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558796250","data":{"timestamp":" 947558796250"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJINA"," userResponse":" MAJINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558796580","data":{"timestamp":" 947558796580"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558797197","data":{"timestamp":" 947558797196"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDHAA"," userResponse":" BIDHAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558798196","data":{"timestamp":" 947558798194"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIVYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558798972","data":{"timestamp":" 947558798971"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAUZA"," userResponse":" ANAUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558801463","data":{"timestamp":" 947558801463"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maneno yao yalinifurahisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANENO"," userResponse":" MANENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558801887","data":{"timestamp":" 947558801887"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maneno yao yalinifurahisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558803251","data":{"timestamp":" 947558803251"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maneno yao yalinifurahisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALINIFURAHISHA"," userResponse":" YALINIFURAHISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558806310","data":{"timestamp":" 947558806309"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558806474","data":{"timestamp":" 947558806474"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558807285","data":{"timestamp":" 947558807285"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558808627","data":{"timestamp":" 947558808626"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALINUNUA"," userResponse":" WALINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558809434","data":{"timestamp":" 947558809434"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINYWAJI"," userResponse":" VINYWAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558812013","data":{"timestamp":" 947558812012"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558812996","data":{"timestamp":" 947558812996"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKANUNUA"," userResponse":" WAKANUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558814137","data":{"timestamp":" 947558814137"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAFUNAJI"," userResponse":" VITAFUNAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558814930","data":{"timestamp":" 947558814930"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558815366","data":{"timestamp":" 947558815365"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558815977","data":{"timestamp":" 947558815976"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558816882","data":{"timestamp":" 947558816880"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUNA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558819701","data":{"timestamp":" 947558819701"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WASIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558819914","data":{"timestamp":" 947558819914"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558820485","data":{"timestamp":" 947558820484"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FEDHA"," userResponse":" FEDHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558821178","data":{"timestamp":" 947558821178"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558821843","data":{"timestamp":" 947558821843"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558822969","data":{"timestamp":" 947558822969"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAZAMA"," userResponse":" WALITAZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558823372","data":{"timestamp":" 947558823372"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558826615","data":{"timestamp":" 947558826615"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" SHUGHULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558826950","data":{"timestamp":" 947558826949"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558827983","data":{"timestamp":" 947558827982"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKATIZWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKATIZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558828206","data":{"timestamp":" 947558828205"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558828665","data":{"timestamp":" 947558828665"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIO"," userResponse":" MLIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558828984","data":{"timestamp":" 947558828983"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558829562","data":{"timestamp":" 947558829559"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HONI"," userResponse":" HONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558830059","data":{"timestamp":" 947558830058"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558830605","data":{"timestamp":" 947558830605"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558831479","data":{"timestamp":" 947558831479"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISHARA"," userResponse":" ISHARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558832084","data":{"timestamp":" 947558832084"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558833060","data":{"timestamp":" 947558833059"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558833930","data":{"timestamp":" 947558833930"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558834804","data":{"timestamp":" 947558834803"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONDOKA"," userResponse":" KUONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558837663","data":{"timestamp":" 947558837663"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" KONDAKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558838573","data":{"timestamp":" 947558838572"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWATAKA"," userResponse":" ALIWATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558839385","data":{"timestamp":" 947558839384"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHUUZI"," userResponse":" WACHUUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558840186","data":{"timestamp":" 947558840186"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONDOKA"," userResponse":" KUONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558840710","data":{"timestamp":" 947558840710"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558840824","data":{"timestamp":" 947558840824"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558841339","data":{"timestamp":" 947558841339"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558844517","data":{"timestamp":" 947558844517"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHUUZI"," userResponse":" WACHUUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558845750","data":{"timestamp":" 947558845750"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISUKUMANA"," userResponse":" WALISUKUMANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558846424","data":{"timestamp":" 947558846424"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558847587","data":{"timestamp":" 947558847587"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" WAKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558848031","data":{"timestamp":" 947558848031"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558848265","data":{"timestamp":" 947558848265"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558848989","data":{"timestamp":" 947558848989"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHUKA"," userResponse":" KUSHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558851437","data":{"timestamp":" 947558851437"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558852072","data":{"timestamp":" 947558852072"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558853485","data":{"timestamp":" 947558853485"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWARUDISHA"," userResponse":" WALIWARUDISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558854218","data":{"timestamp":" 947558854217"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558855074","data":{"timestamp":" 947558855074"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASALIO"," userResponse":" MASALIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558855328","data":{"timestamp":" 947558855328"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558855775","data":{"timestamp":" 947558855775"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELA"," userResponse":" HELA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558856277","data":{"timestamp":" 947558856276"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558858724","data":{"timestamp":" 947558858724"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558859539","data":{"timestamp":" 947558859539"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558860206","data":{"timestamp":" 947558860205"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUHUDI"," userResponse":" JUHUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558860450","data":{"timestamp":" 947558860450"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558861095","data":{"timestamp":" 947558861094"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558861900","data":{"timestamp":" 947558861900"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUZA"," userResponse":" KUUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558862491","data":{"timestamp":" 947558862489"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDHAA"," userResponse":" BIDHAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558862967","data":{"timestamp":" 947558862966"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558865962","data":{"timestamp":" 947558865962"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558867283","data":{"timestamp":" 947558867283"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" LILIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558868279","data":{"timestamp":" 947558868279"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUONI"," userResponse":" KITUONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558869683","data":{"timestamp":" 947558869683"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILICHUNGULIA"," userResponse":" NILICHUNGULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558870526","data":{"timestamp":" 947558870525"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHANI"," userResponse":" DIRISHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558873587","data":{"timestamp":" 947558873587"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" NILIJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558874170","data":{"timestamp":" 947558874169"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558874976","data":{"timestamp":" 947558874975"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEWAHI"," userResponse":" NINGEWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558875622","data":{"timestamp":" 947558875617"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558876438","data":{"timestamp":" 947558876438"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558876901","data":{"timestamp":" 947558876900"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGU"," userResponse":" MWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558877496","data":{"timestamp":" 947558877496"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558880987","data":{"timestamp":" 947558880986"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558882333","data":{"timestamp":" 947558882333"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOENDELEA"," userResponse":" ILIPOENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558883333","data":{"timestamp":" 947558883329"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558884078","data":{"timestamp":" 947558884078"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558884912","data":{"timestamp":" 947558884912"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINGI"," userResponse":" JINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558885407","data":{"timestamp":" 947558885406"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558885526","data":{"timestamp":" 947558885526"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558886091","data":{"timestamp":" 947558886090"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558888980","data":{"timestamp":" 947558888980"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIYAFUMBA"," userResponse":" NILIYAFUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558889475","data":{"timestamp":" 947558889474"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558889957","data":{"timestamp":" 947558889957"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558891263","data":{"timestamp":" 947558891263"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKINUIA"," userResponse":" NIKINUIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558891963","data":{"timestamp":" 947558891962"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558895267","data":{"timestamp":" 947558895267"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558895886","data":{"timestamp":" 947558895886"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWAZO"," userResponse":" MAWAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558896423","data":{"timestamp":" 947558896423"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558897493","data":{"timestamp":" 947558897492"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIREJEA"," userResponse":" YALIREJEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558898412","data":{"timestamp":" 947558898410"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558900720","data":{"timestamp":" 947558900719"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558901927","data":{"timestamp":" 947558901926"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558902763","data":{"timestamp":" 947558902763"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKUWA"," userResponse":" ATAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558903909","data":{"timestamp":" 947558903908"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SALAMA"," userResponse":" SALAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558906254","data":{"timestamp":" 947558906254"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558907128","data":{"timestamp":" 947558907128"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558907872","data":{"timestamp":" 947558907871"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558908895","data":{"timestamp":" 947558908895"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATALETA"," userResponse":" WATALETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558909310","data":{"timestamp":" 947558909309"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELA"," userResponse":" HELA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558910154","data":{"timestamp":" 947558910153"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558912248","data":{"timestamp":" 947558912248"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558913157","data":{"timestamp":" 947558913157"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558913603","data":{"timestamp":" 947558913603"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558914726","data":{"timestamp":" 947558914725"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" ATAKUMBUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558915844","data":{"timestamp":" 947558915844"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYUNYIZIA"," userResponse":" KUNYUNYIZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558916309","data":{"timestamp":" 947558916309"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558916943","data":{"timestamp":" 947558916943"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MICHE"," userResponse":" MICHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558917008","data":{"timestamp":" 947558917008"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558917513","data":{"timestamp":" 947558917512"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558918072","data":{"timestamp":" 947558918072"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558921498","data":{"timestamp":" 947558921497"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558922481","data":{"timestamp":" 947558922481"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKARIRI"," userResponse":" NILIKARIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558923314","data":{"timestamp":" 947558923314"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558923577","data":{"timestamp":" 947558923577"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558924360","data":{"timestamp":" 947558924360"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558925234","data":{"timestamp":" 947558925233"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBANGU"," userResponse":" MJOMBANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558925997","data":{"timestamp":" 947558925996"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558926955","data":{"timestamp":" 947558926954"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558927416","data":{"timestamp":" 947558927416"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558927955","data":{"timestamp":" 947558927955"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558930553","data":{"timestamp":" 947558930553"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558931010","data":{"timestamp":" 947558931009"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558932054","data":{"timestamp":" 947558932053"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJISEMEA"," userResponse":" NAJISEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558932703","data":{"timestamp":" 947558932703"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558933510","data":{"timestamp":" 947558933510"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPATWA"," userResponse":" NILIPATWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558933695","data":{"timestamp":" 947558933695"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558934478","data":{"timestamp":" 947558934478"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" USINGIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558937266","data":{"timestamp":" 947558937266"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558937511","data":{"timestamp":" 947558937510"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558937854","data":{"timestamp":" 947558937853"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558938456","data":{"timestamp":" 947558938455"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558939668","data":{"timestamp":" 947558939668"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIAMSHWA"," userResponse":" NILIAMSHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558939919","data":{"timestamp":" 947558939918"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558940720","data":{"timestamp":" 947558940719"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558940923","data":{"timestamp":" 947558940922"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558941667","data":{"timestamp":" 947558941667"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUITA"," userResponse":" KUITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558942446","data":{"timestamp":" 947558942445"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558943621","data":{"timestamp":" 947558943620"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKWENDA"," userResponse":" WALIOKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558944227","data":{"timestamp":" 947558944227"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558944878","data":{"timestamp":" 947558944878"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558945456","data":{"timestamp":" 947558945455"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558948059","data":{"timestamp":" 947558948058"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" NILICHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558948547","data":{"timestamp":" 947558948547"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558948976","data":{"timestamp":" 947558948975"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558949765","data":{"timestamp":" 947558949764"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558950190","data":{"timestamp":" 947558950190"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558951056","data":{"timestamp":" 947558951055"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558951638","data":{"timestamp":" 947558951638"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558951713","data":{"timestamp":" 947558951713"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558952174","data":{"timestamp":" 947558952173"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558955128","data":{"timestamp":" 947558955127"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558955223","data":{"timestamp":" 947558955223"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558956100","data":{"timestamp":" 947558956100"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558957010","data":{"timestamp":" 947558957008"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558957877","data":{"timestamp":" 947558957877"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAJAA"," userResponse":" LINAJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558958464","data":{"timestamp":" 947558958464"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPESI"," userResponse":" UPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558960764","data":{"timestamp":" 947558960764"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558961377","data":{"timestamp":" 947558961376"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558962029","data":{"timestamp":" 947558962028"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558962923","data":{"timestamp":" 947558962922"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGEANZA"," userResponse":" LINGEANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558963920","data":{"timestamp":" 947558963919"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558964025","data":{"timestamp":" 947558964024"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558964478","data":{"timestamp":" 947558964477"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558965418","data":{"timestamp":" 947558965416"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHARIKI"," userResponse":" MASHARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558967797","data":{"timestamp":" 947558967797"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558967934","data":{"timestamp":" 947558967934"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558968587","data":{"timestamp":" 947558968586"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAANA"," userResponse":" MAANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558969100","data":{"timestamp":" 947558969099"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558969780","data":{"timestamp":" 947558969780"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558970603","data":{"timestamp":" 947558970603"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558971168","data":{"timestamp":" 947558971167"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558971809","data":{"timestamp":" 947558971809"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558972688","data":{"timestamp":" 947558972687"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558973513","data":{"timestamp":" 947558973512"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558973750","data":{"timestamp":" 947558973750"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558974651","data":{"timestamp":" 947558974650"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBANGU"," userResponse":" MJOMBANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558977249","data":{"timestamp":" 947558977248"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558977349","data":{"timestamp":" 947558977348"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 423701e6-df64-44ba-b612-9300702bf7be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBANGU"," userResponse":" MJOMBANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558987427","data":{"timestamp":" 947558987427"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 6cc9624a-7454-40bf-b14b-0100adf5c8e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558991630","data":{"timestamp":" 947558991630"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 6cc9624a-7454-40bf-b14b-0100adf5c8e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_o-ch-d"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558996503","data":{"timestamp":" 947558996503"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 6cc9624a-7454-40bf-b14b-0100adf5c8e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_j-n-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947558996568","data":{"timestamp":" 947558996568"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 6cc9624a-7454-40bf-b14b-0100adf5c8e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_j-n-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559005689","data":{"timestamp":" 947559005688"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_051103"," gameId":" 6cc9624a-7454-40bf-b14b-0100adf5c8e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_j-n-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}